&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：是的，这是一个CSS属性，但是
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So yeah,
it's a CSS property, but
大多数情况下，当您使用它时，您将在JavaScript中使用它。
most of the time when you're using it,
you're gonna use it in JavaScript.
你要进去说，嘿，供你参考，我知道用户要做什么，
You're gonna go in there and say, hey FYI,
I know the user is about to do something,
但我们会想要将其制作成动画。
but we are going to want to animate this.
让我们现在把它放到它自己的层上，然后就可以走了。
Let's get it to its own layer now and
be good to go.
因此，例如，我们可以在鼠标上输入element.style.will Change，
So, for instance we could say on
mouse enter element.style.willChange,
转换会将其提升到自己的层，然后当他们走时，
transform will promote it to its
own layer, and then when they go,
当我们准备好做这件事的时候，
by the time we get it
ready to do the thing,
那么它已经在它自己的层上了，我们可以走了。
then it's already on its own layer,
we're good to go.
因此，如果它像侧边栏或粘性底部，则使用CSS。
So, if it's like a sidebar or
the sticky bottom, use CSS.
但如果它只会像你一样暂时成为它自己的一层
But if it's something that's only going to
become its own layer temporarily as you do
一些动画，然后它会回到一个静态的位置，
some animation and
then it's going back to a static position,
我们将添加will Change，我们将执行该操作，然后将其放回原处。
we'll add the willChange, we'll do
the thing and then we'll put it back.
再说一次，我们做完之后我们想自己清理一下，
And again, after we're done we
wanna clean up after ourselves,
因为如果鼠标悬停在其上方一次，鼠标就会进入，形成自己的层。
because if they hover over it once and
mouse enters, make its own layer.
你忘了把它放回去，你最终会有很多层。
And you forget to put it back down,
you're gonna end up with a lot of layers.
我们说过这是件坏事。
We talked about that's a bad thing.
所以这里有一个例子，好的，鼠标进入，好吗？
So here's an example, okay,
mouse enter, all right?
是的，让我们设置转换和
Yeah let's set the transform and
然后可能是动画结束的时候，对，把它放回去。
then may be when the animation ends,
right, put it back down.
好了，我们完成了，它不需要再是它自己的一层了，
All right, we're done, it doesn't
need to be its own layer anymore,
我们可以走了。
we're good to go.
好的，那我们那时就可以做了。
All right, so we can do it then.
然后我可以说，这真的是额外的加分，
And then I arguably,
it would be really extra bonus points,
你也应该有这个，就像一个鼠标离开，也把它放下。
you should have this as well, is like
on a mouse leave, also put it down.
鼠标，这将是一个当他们点击它时会移动的方框，好吗？
Mouseenters, this would be a box that
moves when they click on it, all right?
鼠标中心，让我们把它移到一个区域图层，他们点击了吗？
Mouseenters, let's move it to
a zone layer, they clicked?
酷，做动画。
Cool, do the animation.
动画完成了？
Animation's done?
把它放下，老鼠走了？
Put it back down, the mouse's left?
把它放回去，对吗？
Put it back down, right?
而且因为我们没有做任何其他的事情，当鼠标中心，是的，
And because we are not doing anything
else, when the mouseenters, yeah,
我们正在做一些工作，但在需要之前我们正在做这些工作。
we are doing some work, but we are doing
that work before it is needed.
我们等待，直到我们准备好开始动画，它可能看起来有点欢乐，
We wait until we are ready to start
animating, it could look a little jolty,
因为它就像我的上帝，我要把这个放到它自己的一层。
cuz it's like my God I gotta
get this to its own layer.
现在我必须移动它，对吧，而不是在你需要它之前移动它或者
And now I've gotta move it, right,
versus move it before you need it or
在你需要它之前将它移动到它自己的层，当你需要它的时候设置它的动画。
move it to it's own layer before you need
it, animate it when you're supposed to.
完成后把它放回去。
Put it back down when you're done.